SHUNTIA REED MEDICAL ASSISTANT DIALYSIS TECHNICIAN UNIT SECRETARY

205 Dove Rd Jacksonville Ark, 72076 • (501)501-541-7047 • woodsshuntia@yahoo.com

SUMMARY

Dedicated, skilled MA with a broad range of healthcare experience. Background in front office, acute and long-term care with some experience in sterilization techniques, and specimen collection and handling. Self-motivated professional committed to providing quality nursing care.

SKILLS/EXPIERENCE

- ❖ Flexible, quick learner who adapts easily to new situations and enjoys a challenge
- ❖ Quality direct and indirect support while maintaining professionalism
- ❖ Good problem solving ability and analytic skill to solve the problem efficiently
- ❖ Patient Care and Personal Hygiene alone with the ability to Assist and/or instruct patient as needed
- ❖ Team leader with excellent interaction skill to coordinate and work within a team
- ❖ Strong Organizational and Communication skills both orally and in writing
- ❖ Basic Office Computer Skills such as data entry, calendar and scheduling programs, database, spreadsheet, word processing, e-mail and desktop publishing applications
- General Office Skills including the ability to file, make photocopies, post outgoing mail, sort and distribute incoming mail, sign for deliveries and send faxes
- ❖ Take detailed phone messages and keep accurate paper and electronic records

CERTIFICATIONS

Basic Life Support	2015	
EDUCATION		
Stuttgart High School, Stuttgart, AR * High School Diploma	May 2003	
Remington College, Little Rock, AR * Medical Assisting Diploma	February 2006 -Nov 2006	
Pulaski Technical College, Little Rock, AR	Aug. 2016	

General education courses

WORK HISTORY

Davita Dialysis * Operating the machines and monitoring the patients undergoing treatment	Dialysis Tech	Oct.2016 (current position)
North Metro Medical Center * Administrative duties * Clerical duties	Unit Secretary in ICU	Mar. 2014 - Oct. 2016
Arkansas Children's Hospital Surgical Department Support Transported and Monitored children with behavioral health disorders	Medical Assistant	Feb. 2012 - Jan. 2014
Baptist Health Rehabilitation Institute * ADL care experience * Patient Care and Hygiene	Medical Assistant	Jun. 2009 - Nov. 2011
University of Arkansas for Medical Sciences ❖ Performed Bone Marrow and Aspiration Procedure	Medical Assistant	Feb. 2007 - Feb. 2009

REFERENCES

Available upon request